<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crunchy Data Postgres Operator on Crunchy Data PostgreSQL Operator Documentation</title>
    <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/stable/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crunchy Data Postgres Operator on Crunchy Data PostgreSQL Operator Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/stable/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration Resources</title>
      <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/stable/configuration/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/stable/configuration/configuration/</guid>
      <description>The operator is template-driven; this makes it simple to configure both the client and the operator.
conf Directory The Operator is configured with a collection of files found in the conf directory. These configuration files are deployed to your Kubernetes cluster when the Operator is deployed. Changes made to any of these configuration files currently require a redeployment of the Operator on the Kubernetes cluster.
The server components of the Operator include Role Based Access Control resources which need to be created a single time by a Kubernetes cluster-admin user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PGO YAML</title>
      <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/stable/configuration/pgo-yaml-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/stable/configuration/pgo-yaml-configuration/</guid>
      <description>pgo.yaml Configuration The pgo.yaml file contains many different configuration settings as described in this section of the documentation.
The pgo.yaml file is broken into major sections as described below:
Cluster    Setting Definition     BasicAuth if set to true will enable Basic Authentication   PrimaryNodeLabel newly created primary deployments will specify this node label if specified, unless you override it using the &amp;ndash;node-label command line flag, if not set, no node label is specifed   ReplicaNodeLabel newly created replica deployments will specify this node label if specified, unless you override it using the &amp;ndash;node-label command line flag, if not set, no node label is specifed   CCPImagePrefix newly created containers will be based on this image prefix (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating Documentation</title>
      <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/stable/contributing/documentation-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/stable/contributing/documentation-updates/</guid>
      <description>Documentation The documentation website is generated using Hugo and https://pages.github.com/)[GitHub Pages]().
Hosting Hugo Locally (Optional) If you would like to build the documentation locally, view the official Installing Hugo guide to set up Hugo locally.
You can then start the server by running the following commands -
cd $COROOT/hugo/ hugo server  The local version of the Hugo server is accessible by default from localhost:1313. Once you&amp;rsquo;ve run hugo server, that will let you interactively make changes to the documentation as desired and view the updates in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submitting Issues</title>
      <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/stable/contributing/issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/stable/contributing/issues/</guid>
      <description>If you would like to submit an feature / issue for us to consider please submit an to the official GitHub Repository.
If you would like to work the issue, please add that information in the issue so that we can confirm we are not already working no need to duplicate efforts.
If you have any question you can submit a Support - Question and Answer issue and we will work with you on how you can get more involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submitting Pull Requests</title>
      <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/stable/contributing/pull-requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/stable/contributing/pull-requests/</guid>
      <description>So you decided to submit an issue and work it. Great! Let&amp;rsquo;s get it merged in to the codebase. The following will go a long way to helping get the fix merged in quicker.
 Create a Pull Request from your Fork to the Develop branch. Update the checklists in the Pull Request Description. Reference which issues this Pull Request is resolving.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>