<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installation on Crunchy Data PostgreSQL Operator Documentation</title>
    <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/latest/installation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installation on Crunchy Data PostgreSQL Operator Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/latest/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Operator Installation</title>
      <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/latest/installation/operator-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/latest/installation/operator-install/</guid>
      <description>A full installation of the Operator includes the following steps:
 create a project structure configure your environment variables configure Operator templates create security resources deploy the operator install pgo CLI (end user command tool)  Operator end-users are only required to install the pgo CLI client on their host and can skip the server-side installation steps. pgo CLI clients are provided on the Github Releases page for Linux, Mac, and Windows clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer Setup</title>
      <link>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/latest/installation/developer-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunchydata.github.io/postgres-operator/latest/installation/developer-setup/</guid>
      <description>Developing The Postgres-Operator is an open source project hosted on GitHub.
Developers that wish to build the Operator from source or contribute to the project via pull requests would set up a development environment through the following steps.
Create Kubernetes Cluster We use either OpenShift Container Platform or kubeadm to install development clusters.
Create a Local Development Host We currently build on CentOS 7 and RHEL 7 hosts. Others operating systems are possible, however we do not support building or running the Operator on other operating systems at this time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>